<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Serak International Asia</title>
    <link>http://www.serakasia.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Serak International Asia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 23:01:16 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.serakasia.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Serak International</title>
      <link>http://www.serakasia.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 23:01:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.serakasia.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About Serak International Asia Serak Asia is a not-for-profit regional affiliate of VDT Serak International (see below) formed in 2015. The purpose of Serak Asia is to promote and advance the study and practice of Pukulan Pentjak Silat Serak in Asia, by forming training groups, and helping to develop training group leaders, coordinators and instructors to teach Serak in their local communities. As more and more training groups form in a particular country, then it is expected that a national affliate will be formed for that country, and that eventually Serak Asia will be more involved in regional coordination to the point where the national affiliates will take on more of the direct responsibility for promoting and developing high quality instructors, schools and training groups in their particular countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protect what you love</title>
      <link>http://www.serakasia.com/blog/2017/11/11/protect-what-you-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.serakasia.com/blog/2017/11/11/protect-what-you-love/</guid>
      <description>Beladiri - Personal Protection  The true soldier fights not because he hates what is in front of him, but because he loves what is behind him. — G.K. Chesterton.
 People approach martial arts training with different goals in mind. A great many people seek an interesting way to maintain health and engage in various forms of physical culture: strength, cardio/fitness, flexibility, and so on. Others are attracted to competitive and sportive opportunities that are offered within many modern martial arts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Think Strategically</title>
      <link>http://www.serakasia.com/blog/2017/11/10/think-strategically/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.serakasia.com/blog/2017/11/10/think-strategically/</guid>
      <description>Strategy without tactics is the slowest route to victory, tactics without strategy is the noise before defeat. — Sun Tzu, Ancient Chinese military strategist 
Perception is strong and sight weak. In strategy it is important to see distant things as if they were close and to take a distanced view of close things. — Miyamoto Musashi, Japanese swordsman
 To truly understand a particular system of martial arts it is necessary to first appreciate the strategy underlying the choice of tactics &amp;amp; techniques that are typically employed within that style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools &amp; Training Groups</title>
      <link>http://www.serakasia.com/groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 22:06:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.serakasia.com/groups/</guid>
      <description>Serak International Markas (Headquarters) - Maha Guru Horatio Rodriquez
VDT Serak International
4651 suite A Gage Ave
Bell CA. 90201 USA
Email: horacio@serakasia.com
Web: http://serak.com
Thailand Chiang Mai - Guru Nyk Cowham Tel: (local) 099-476-2009 Tel: (outside Thailand) +66 99-476-2009 Email: nyk@serakasia.com Web: http://serakthai.wordpress.com
Surat Thani - Mas Jay Griggs
Denmark Copenhagen - Mas Andreas Kaaber (Instructor)
Email: andy@serakasia.com
United States of America California Marina Del Rey - Ustad Dan Inosanto (Ustad Guru Serak)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangkok Seminar: October 2015</title>
      <link>http://www.serakasia.com/events/2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 20:54:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.serakasia.com/events/2015/</guid>
      <description>The first annual Serak seminar in Thailand was held over the weekend at the Boxer Rebellion Bangkok Boxing Center in Bangkok. Our thanks go out to Maha Guru Horacio Rodriguez for bearing 100% humidity and a tropical storm to share some of his vast knowledge and skill with us. Also special thanks go to Mas Andreas Kaaber for helping to construct and transport our not-so-portable Pantjar and for always being on hand to help make things run well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Well in Every Way</title>
      <link>http://www.serakasia.com/blog/2017/11/09/live-well-in-every-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.serakasia.com/blog/2017/11/09/live-well-in-every-way/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work With What You Have</title>
      <link>http://www.serakasia.com/blog/2017/11/08/with-what-you-have/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.serakasia.com/blog/2017/11/08/with-what-you-have/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work With What Comes</title>
      <link>http://www.serakasia.com/blog/2017/11/07/with-what-comes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.serakasia.com/blog/2017/11/07/with-what-comes/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have a Playful Attitude</title>
      <link>http://www.serakasia.com/blog/2017/11/06/playful-attitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 22:22:55 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.serakasia.com/blog/2017/11/06/playful-attitude/</guid>
      <description>This is new content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.serakasia.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.serakasia.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you We are very welcoming towards people who are new to martial arts training and very happy to answer any quetions that you might have, without any obligation or pressure. Please feel free to contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>http://www.serakasia.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.serakasia.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>